good morning everyone I hope you've had
a lovely week over here there's much
preparations for winter it is chilly and
the air smells a pine and damp soil
today I'm digging up some potatoes with
my father at a store for the winter and
looking forward to adding to some soups
and stews on cold Frozen nights when I
want to curl up by the fire and put
something warm in my
belly
basically look at that see
[Music]
that Earth oh you got to go deep
recently in the wake of so much change
once again coming into my world I've
been looking back on how for much of my
life I've resisted change and often
deemed it unwelcome everything from
moving to a new home leaving an
unfulfilling relationship or stepping
out of my comfort zone in a small way
was so
hard and change can be hard
understandably in many ways it will
always be to let go of what we know and
accept the risks of stepping out into
the unknown as I've embarked on a
journey of growth trying to live my life
fully without letting fear hold me back
I found it quite helpful to to shift my
mindset instead of focusing on what I'm
losing when it comes to life changes I
could instead focus on what I'm gaining
I've thought about it in regards to
Parenthood I have received feedback from
some people in my life on how I will
lose a lot in starting this new era so
much that I will never gain back but
I've never found it helpful to think
that way what I do find helpful is
wondering not so much what I'll lose but
what I'll gain and find joy in that so
perhaps this mindset was not helpful to
you we're all different but if it is I
personally have found it quite rewarding
to see change in this way because
whether we like it or not change forces
itself upon us and it's up to us on how
we respond to it and if we're able to
bloom where we're planted setting down
Roots finding the richness in our new
soil and beginning a
[Music]
new
so as you can see it is looking defin
itely like late Autumn all the leaves
have already fallen from the Aspens and
everything's been bitten by the frost I
would love to find some Little Treasures
to decorate my fairy house with and I'm
going to show you the project once I get
home but I'm looking for little pine
cones and leaves and anything else
nature might provide so that is why I'm
here today I am looking forward to going
home and getting cozy and working on my
project so I'm going to take you along
and let's see what we
[Music]
find when I started my journey to Better
Health making consistent Lifestyle
Changes seem nearly impossible but it
only felt that way when I looked far
into the future if I only challenged
myself to living one day 1 hour a little
more free than the one before it was
suddenly more feasible and I slowly
started to gain confidence that I can
face life I can deal with the unknown
with ups and downs Joy and Pain and it's
just about taking it one day at a time
it's surprising how far you can go
perhaps you might roll your eyes at the
Simplicity of this idea but in my case I
find the simplest practices often lead
to places you never thought you'd
go
[Music]
right
so I've been working on this for about
half an hour and I was going to do very
detailed things I had all these plans
but I just I really enjoyed the
Simplicity it reminded me a lot of a
fairy house I made when I was a child
and so I thought I would show it to you
here you
go it has some Apothecary
bottles and a lot of rose hips I really
loved how the little rose hips looked I
think I think it is very sweet so maybe
this will inspire you to get a little
bit crafty this
November
[Music]
I have a bit of a mess behind me as I
have been crafting all day and for some
some reason I always create a tornado of
just chaos whenever I do that however I
did want to say some huge words of thank
you to those who uh sent us some baby
items uh since my last video there were
so many practical as well as beautiful
items and I appreciate it so much Luke
as well wanted to say a huge thank you
personally on camera but he has been
very sick this week he is incredibly
grateful nonetheless there are some such
cute little items as well as um some
washcloths and all sorts of little
things and it has really prepared us for
the future so thank you so so much it is
getting so cold out and it is starting
to feel very very cozy at home it's
actually hard to leave so I've been
doing a lot of resting reading managing
how I've been feeling and it's been a
interesting Journey it's so far it's
been incredibly rewarding I think I'm
going to go out and check out how the
fairy house is looking in the evening
and in the Twilight the project
definitely ignited my childlike Wonder
so I absolutely have to go outside now
with a lantern to enjoy the nighttime
[Music]
ambiance